SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Afanasy Barbarov

GO·NODEJS·AWS·REACT·SERVERLESS

SUMMARY

I'm a Software Engineer with more than 10 years of programming experience. I've been developing web solutions and automating business processes using Go, JavaScript, AWS, React, C#/.NET. I work closely with clients to define ideas and deliver products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER, REMOTE - 2020-2021

- Integrated Stripe payments, integrated Agora video chats. Migrated codebase from .NET to NodeJS.
- Configured CI/CD with Terraform and GitHub actions and infrastructure as a code.
- Created a service for automated submission and processing of trademarks.
 Integrated Robokassa payments.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER, APALEO (<u>APALEO.COM</u>), REMOTE (CONTRACT) – 2019-2020

- Implemented invoicing and payment reports (using Chargebee). Created couple of apps for the apaleo store. Configured integration testing of microservices. Integrated Adyen payments.
- Created and documented APIs. Bootstrapped a CLI that uses APIs. Participated in API design sessions.

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER, TEKLABS – 2013-2019

- Created UI widgets. Created Swagger UI plugins.
- Configured integration and e2e testing.
- Created one of the biggest Nordic data exchange APIs.
- Migrated existing .NET services to .NET Core.

.NET DEVELOPER, ETNA SOFTWARE (ETNASOFT.COM) - 2012-2013

 Created widgets for financial analytics of a trading app — charts, grids, pivot tables, both back-end and front-end.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, TIRS - 2010-2012

 Created drivers for ARM processors; created a prototype of softwaredefined radio (SDR); created testing tools for printed circuit boards.

EDUCATION

Ivanovo State Power University (ISPU), Russia — Master's Degree in Applied Mathematics and Computer Science, Mathematical modelling, 2005-2009

TECHNOLOGIES & SKILLS

- Go/JavaScript/Typescript/NodeJS/C#/.NET/MSSQL/MySQL/MongoDB/ Terraform/Docker/AWS Lambda/DynamoDB/Microservices/REST/Angular/ React/Vue
- AWS certified (AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate)
- Microsoft certified (MVC/HTML/CSS)